Cody Derbyshire

Front-End Developer + Digital Designer focused on Accessibility & Interactivity.

https://codyderbyshire.com

⊕ Wellington, New Zealand

derbyshire@outlook.co.nz

+64220725530



2017 - 2017

About

As a Front-End Developer + Digital Designer, I pride myself on making fun and accessible products. I'm always eager to learn and love feedback. Currently, I work mostly with Javascript, React, Node.js, Framer Motion and react-three-fiber. I have over 5 years of experience as a Designer and a 2 years as a Developer.

Work Experience

Scale Studios 2020 - 2022

In-house Designer + Manufacturer

Designed + manufactured props and set-dressing elements for film and television. Technologies: 3D printing, Fusion 360, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Blender, Rhino, Lasercutting, CNC Machining

Work featured in Avatar 2, Rings of Power, X, Pearl, and Evil Dead Rise

Freelance Design 2018 - Current

Digital Designer

Creation of but not limited to websites, business cards, branding, posters, pamphelets, invitations, and user experiences. Technologies: Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Squarespace, Javascript, React, HTML, CSS

Branding & Marketing for Toi Whakaari Manifest showcase, Website and UX for Toi Whakaari Festival of Work in Development 2020

Education

Whitecliffe College	2023 - 2023
Diploma in Web Development and Design	
Yoobee College	2022 - 2022
NZ Certificate in Information Technology (Level 5)	
Toi Whakaari	2018 - 2020
Bachelor of Design	

Diploma of Costume Design + Construction

Melbourne Polytechnic

Skills

JavaScript CSS React/Next.js Node.js Illustrator Photoshop Fusion 360

Projects

Black Garlic Furniture •

Webstore proof of concept using Framer Motion and Spline for interactive UX

Side Project React Next.js

Vite Framer Motion Spline

codyderbyshire.com •

Personal website and portfolio. Built with React and ThreeJS

Side Project Vite React

Framer Motion ThreeJS

Poke-API •

Gen I + II Pokedex built using React and the PokeAPI

Side Project Vite React

PokeAPI

Inky •

Chatbot built to help user decide on a tattoo style

Side Project Javascript

@FONT-FACE •

Webstore built to test Stripe integration

Side Project React Stripe